MUHAMMAD NAUFAL KATENI

$\underline{(+62)816382001}|\ \underline{naufalkateni2001@gmail.com}|\ \underline{GitHub}\ |\ \underline{GitLab}\ |\ \underline{LinkedIn}$

SUMMARY

I am a fresh graduate who has an interest in back-end developers. Skilled in building web based application and know the technique about identifying database, fundamental programming, version control system, and API management along with API documentation and API testing. Have experience in building website with Node.js, Express and a bit of TypeScript

EXPERIENCE

Suitmedia Digital Agency

Software Engineer Intern

Palembang, ID Online Aug 2022 – Dec 2022

- This is an internship program from Suitmedia that I got from Kampus Merdeka
 program. I got this program on the third batch and I choose Software Engineer intern for
 5 months from August 2022 to December 2022
- The internship program is conducted on a project basis using real projects. On the project
 I handled bug fixes, modified existing small features, and created new small to medium
 scale features. In addition, the project implemented daily scrum which made the progress
 of the project easy to monitor.

Binar Academy

JavaScript Backend Independent Study

 This is an independent study from Binar Academy that I got from Kampus Merdeka program. I got this program on the second batch and I choose JavaScript Backend to study for 5 months from February 2022 to July 2022 Palembang, ID Online Feb 2022 – Jul 2022

Palembang, ID *On-site*

Dec 2021 - Jan 2022

- This program teach us from the basic of Backend Development, Node.js, Rest API, MVC
 Architecture, documentation, tesing, deployment, and CI/CD. From this program, I got 8
 challenge to practice and improve my programming skill. All of the callenge can be seen
 on my GitLab, then I also got a team project for final project that consist of front-end part
 and back-end part.
- My final project can be seen on my <u>secondhand-be</u> repository

Poltekkes Kemenkes Palembang

Intern

- Along with my group colleagues for Kerja Praktek course from college, we buit a registration form website for new student called <u>Sipenmaru</u>
- The website built with CodeIgniter 3 and PostgreSQL as database so we can easily deploy the webiste to Heroku

SKILL

Programming: JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, Express, PHP, Laravel, CodeIgniter, OOP, Functional Programming, Rest API, API Documentation, API Testing, GitLab CI/CD, Unit Testing, Integration Testing

Database: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB

Web Development: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS

Cloud Provider: Heroku

Others: Git, GitHub, GitLab, Postman, Swagger, Regexp

EDUCATION

Sriwijaya University

Computer Science, Informatic Engineer

• GPA: 3.67 out of 4 (Cumlaude)

Palembang, ID

Aug 2019 – 2023

ORGANIZATION

DPM KM FACULTY SRIWIJAYA UNIVERSITY

Staff of the Division of Budget

Palembang, ID Apr 2020 – Jan 2021

LANGUAGE

Indonesian (Native Language)

English (Fluent)